Guide to the Cherríe Moraga Papers, 1970-1996
Department of Special Collections
- Series IV. Correspondence
  - Subseries b. Business
    - Kitchen Table: Women of Color Press [Smith, Barbara] [contains documents re: Audre Lorde] [1 of 3] n.d. (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Kitchen Table: Women of Color Press [Smith, Barbara] [contains documents re: Audre Lorde] [2 of 3] n.d. (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Kitchen Table: Women of Color Press [Smith, Barbara] [contains documents re: Audre Lorde] [3 of 3] n.d. (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Kless, Downing [Tufts University Department of Drama] 1995 (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - Larsen, Jesse 1994 (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Letters of recommendation for Cherríe Moraga n.d. (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Marks, Milton, California State Senator 1991 Mar. 1 (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Metropolitan State College Center for Visual Arts 1992 (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - Migrant Media Productions ["Watsonville on Strike"] [Silver, John] 1995 Apr. (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - Miller, Leilani T. J. [University of Hawai'i, Hilo] 1992 (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - Mountain Star Productions, Hollywood [Fishman, Joan] 1991 Sept. (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - National Women's History Project 1992 Apr. -May (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - New York Asian Women's Center 1993 Sept. (Box 4, Folder 43)
    - Pelosi, Nancy, United States Congresswoman 1993 Mar. (Box 4, Folder 44)
    - Persephone Press n.d. (Box 4, Folder 45)
    - Phillippides, Julie Foraker [re: 14th Chicano Literary Festival] 1988 Apr. 18 -25 (Box 4, Folder 46)
    - Retana, Robert G. [Fuerza Magazine] 1994 (Box 4, Folder 47)
    - Rice, Felicia [re: Lenguas Sueltas: poemas / Elba Rosario Sánchez y otras] 1994 Nov. (Box 4, Folder 48)
    - Robinson, Jonathan ["¡Oye Familia!: a dialogue with society"] [1 of 2] 1994 Sept. (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Robinson, Jonathan ["¡Oye Familia!: a dialogue with society"] [1 of 2] 1994 Sept. (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Robinson, Jonathan ["¡Oye Familia!: a dialogue with society"] [2 of 2] 1994 Sept. (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Saenz, Diana n.d. (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Serpent Source Foundation for Woemn Artists 1994 Feb. 9 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Signs: journal of woemn in culture and society 1991 July (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Socialist Review [includes Haraway, Donna. "A manifesto for cyborgs"] 1985 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Soto, Gary [Arte Americas] 1994 July 30 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - South End Press 1991 -1995 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Southern California Women for Understanding 1991 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Stanford University Committe on Black Performing Arts 1994 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Stanford University [Elam, Harry] [re: teaching position] 1995 Mar. (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Sundquist, Eric [UCLA Department of English] 1994 June 10 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Sundquist, Eric UCLA Dept of English 1994 June 10 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - University of California, Santa Cruz 1994 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Warner Brothers Television 1993 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Whipple, Elizabeth 1995 Aug. 28 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Wilson, Allan J. [Carol Publishing Group] [re: Novas, Himilee. The Hispanic 100] 1995 Feb. -Mar. (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Women of color mailing lists n.d. (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Women's Center [fax to Sima] 1995 Mar. 3 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Women's Press, Toronto 1994 Feb. 14 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Permissions requests: Adams, Maurianne. Social Diversity. Dubuque, Iowa: Kendall/Hunt Publishing Company ["La güera"] 1994 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Permissions requests: Andersen, Margaret & Patricia Hill Collins, eds. Race, Class, and Gender: an anthology. Wadsworth Publishing Company ["La güera"] 1994 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Permissions requests: Arizmendi, Yareli. Who buys your shoes. [excerpt from: "Giving up the ghost"] 1988 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Permissions requests: Barrington, Judith, ed. An intimate wilderness: lesbian writers on sexuality. Portland, Oregon: Eighth Mountain Press ["For you, mamá..."] 1994 Jan. (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Permissions requests: Besenjak, Cheryl. The woman that I am. St. Martin's Press ["The welder"] 1993 May 28 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Permissions requests: Cassidy, Marsh. The book of scenes for aspiring actors. National Textbook Company [scene from Shadow of a man] 1994 June 14 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Permissions requests: Castillo-Speed, Lillian. Latinas. Simon & Schuster ["Art in América con Acento"] 1994 Jan. 13 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Permissions requests: Comstock, Gary D. Gay theology without apology. Pilgrim Press ["The welder"] 1993 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Permissions requests: Cullinan, Mary & Eileen Barrett, eds. American Women Writers. New York: St. Martin's Press ["Pesadilla"] 1991 Aug. 20 (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Permissions requests: Daniels, Rebecca. St. Lawrence University, Canton, New York [staged reading of Heroes and Saints] 1995 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Permissions requests: Davis, Deborah. Women, Culture, and Society. Dubuque, Iowa: Kendall/Hunt Publishing Company ["La güera"] 1993 May (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Permissions requests: de Lauretis, Teresa. The Practice of Love. Indiana University Press [excerpt from Giving up the ghost: teatro in two acts] 1993 -1994 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Permissions requests: Equal Means Journal ["The welder"] 1992 Oct. 8 (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Permissions requests: Fernández, Roberta. Arte Publico Press [Loving in the war years] 1993 July 28 (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - Permissions requests: Foster, David William. Anthology of Chicano Literature. New York: Garland Publishing, Inc. ["La güera"] 1994 Dec. 23 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Permissions requests: Giard, Robert. Particular Voices: Portraits of Gay and Lesbian Writers. [photograph of CM] n.d. (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Permissions requests: Goldberger, Nancy & Jody Verloff. Essential Papers in Cultural Psychology. New York: New York University Press ["La güera"] 1994 (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - Permissions requests: Holoch, Naomi & Joan Nestle, eds. Women on Women. New York: New American Library 1992 (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - Permissions requests: Howe, Florence & Ellen Bass, eds. No more masks! New York: HarperCollins ["For the color of my mother" and "Loving in the war years"] 1992 Oct. (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - Permissions requests: Kaschak, Ellen. Engendered Meanings. New York: BasicBooks [excerpt from "Loving in the war years"] 1991 (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - Permissions requests: La Raza Graphics, San Francisco [image of CM] 1994 May 23 (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - Permissions requests: Martin, Wendy, ed. Best Essays by American Women. 1993 Nov. 15 (Box 5, Folder 41)
    - Permissions requests: Newman, Lesléa, ed. Contemporary Lesbian Love Poems. Ballentine Books ["If" and "Loving in the war years"] 1995 Feb. 18 (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - Permissions requests: Nölle-Fischer, Karen, ed. Mit verschärftem Blick: Feministische Literarurkritik. München: Frauenoffensive Verlag GmbH [German translation rights to "Loving in the war years"] 1991 (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - Permissions requests: Pearlberg, Gerry Gomez, ed. Great Lesbian Love Poems. New York: St. Martin's Press ["Loving in the war years"] 1994 (Box 5, Folder 44)
    - Permissions requests: Perales, Marían. "Empowering 'The Welder': An historical survey of women of color in the West," in Jameson & Armitage, eds. Women's West. 2d edition. ["The Welder"] 1994 Aug. 1 (Box 5, Folder 45)
    - Permissions requests: Kathy Perkins and Roberta Uno, eds. Contemporary Plays by Women of Color. Routledge [Heroes & Saints] 1994 Aug. 15 (Box 5, Folder 46)
    - Permissions requests: Poetry Flash [photo request] 1994 Aug. 1 (Box 5, Folder 47)
    - Permissions requests: Portland State University [reproduction of Heroes & Saints] 1994 Aug. 1 (Box 5, Folder 48)
    - Permissions requests: Rebolledo, Tey Diana & Eliana Rivero, eds. Infinite Divisions: an anthology of Chicana literature. University of Arizona Press ["For the color of my mother"] 1991 (Box 5, Folder 49)
    - Permissions requests: Rothenberg, Paula S. & Alison M. Jaggar, eds. Feminist Frameworks, 3d edition. McGraw-Hill ["A long line of Vendidas"] 1991 (Box 5, Folder 50)
    - Permissions requests: Schiffman, Jessica & O'Toole, Laura L. Gender Violence: Interdisciplinary Perspectives. New York: New York University Press ["Anatomy Lesson"] 1995 (Box 5, Folder 51)
    - Permissions requests: Schniedewind, Nancy, et al. Women's Images and Realities: a Multicultural Anthology of Women in the United States. Mayfield Publishing Company ["A long line of Vendidas" & "Traitor begets traitor"] 1991 Sept. 3 (Box 5, Folder 52)
    - Permissions requests: Schuster, Charles & William Van Pelt. Speculations: Culture, Identity, and Change. Blair Press ["The Welder"] 1992 Mar. (Box 5, Folder 53)
    - Permissions requests: Sinister Wisdom ["It's the poverty" & "Until they burn all the books"] 1991 Feb. (Box 5, Folder 54)
    - Permissions requests: Stavans, Ilan. untitled essay. Transition.-- No. 65 (1995 Winter) ["Peloncito"] 1994 (Box 5, Folder 55)
    - Permissions requests: St. Joan, Jacqueline & Annette B. McElhiney, eds. Beyond Portia: A Feminist Reader in Law and Literature. ["The Welder" & "For the color of my mother"] 1991 Feb. (Box 5, Folder 56)
    - Permissions requests: Torres, Gabriel, University of California, Davis [reproduction for class use of "For an art of resistance"] 1994 (Box 5, Folder 57)
    - Permissions requests: Turoff, Randy, ed. Lesbian Words: State of the art anthology. New York: Richard Kasak ["The breakdown of the bicultural mind"] 1994 (Box 5, Folder 58)
    - Permissions requests: Women's Studies: Thinking Women. Dubuque, Iowa: Kendall/Hunt Publishing Company ["The welder"] 1991 Nov. (Box 5, Folder 59)
- Series V. Gigs
  - 2nd National 3rd world lesbian / gay conference & 2nd National Coalition of Black Gays General Convention, Chicago 1981 Nov. 27 -29 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Aguero, Kathleen [Kitchen Table: Women of Color Press] [request for contribution] 1982 July 27 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Aguilas [reading / speaking] n.d. (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - American Booksellers Association [reading / speaking] 1994 Apr. (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - American Ethnological Society [Rofel, Lisa] [reading / speaking] 1992 Dec. 2 -6 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Anderson, Margaret & Patricia Hill Collins, eds. Race, Class, & Gender [publishing] 1994 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Appalachian State University [Caballero, Soledad] [written interview] 1994 July (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Arizona State University [Candelaria, Cordelia] [reading / speaking] 1994 Feb. 4 -Mar. 5 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Arroyo Books / Libreria Arroyo [Gillette, Christopher J.] [reading / speaking] 1993 Sept. 28 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Association for Women in Psychology [Lopez-Trevino, Naria Elena] [speaking] 1991 Jan. 17 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Awards [1 of 2] n.d. (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Awards [2 of 2] n.d. (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Balboa High School, San Francisco [Sanchez, Gil] [production] 1994 Mar. (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Bates College [Detwiler, Susan] [reading / speaking] 1995 Mar. (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Bay Package Productions [Stohler, Scott] [publishing] n.d. (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Bilingual Foundation for the Arts [Reyes, Guillermo] [production] 1992 Nov. 18 -1993 Mar. 4 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Brandt, Kate. Happy Endings: Lesbian Writers Talk about theur lives and work [interview request] 1991 Apr. -1992 Apr. (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - California Arts Council [panel appearance] 1988 Feb. 23 -1993 Feb. 16 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - California College of Arts and Crafts, Oakland n.d. (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - California Latino Theater "Creating and recreating an American image" [speaking request] n.d. (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - California Rehabilitation Center [reading / speaking] 1987 Mar. 27 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - California State University, Fresno [reading / speaking] n.d. (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - El Mensajaro [interview] n.d. (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - California State University, Long Beach [reading / speaking] 1994 May 6 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - California State University, Northridge [reading / speaking] 1994 Apr. 28 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - California State University, Sacramento [reading / speaking] 1995 May 4 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Camp Trans [Burkholder, Nancy Jean] [reading / speaking] 1994 June 8 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Center for Lesbian and Gay Studies, CUNY [reading / speaking] 1995 Apr. 27 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Modern Times Book Store, San Francisco [reading] 1994 Oct. 27 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Center for the Arts, Yerba Buena Gardens, San Francisco[request for essay] 1992 Jan. 8 -1993 Mar. 19 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Center for Women and Religion, Berkeley [Gillan, María Mazziotti] [reading request] 1995 Feb. 9 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - El Centro su Teatro [production] 1994 Sept. 1 -Nov. 7 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Chicana / Latina Research Institute, University of California, Davis [speaking request] 1995 Aug. (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - College of Marin [Diaz, María Dolores] n.d. (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Colorado College [Sanchez, Kinberly] [request for conference appearance, Cultural and Gender perspectives] 1995 Feb. 7 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Committee for Health Rights in the Americas [Chiszak, Lucinda] [speaking request] 1995 Feb. 21 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Cornell University Gays, Bisexuals, & Lesbians of Color [GBLOC] [reading / speaking request] 1995 Apr. 22 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Dartmouth College Gay, Lesbian, Bisexual Organization [reading / speaking] 1995 May 5 -7 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - De Ambiente [Roque, Horacio] [reading / speaking] 1994 Mar. 11 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Different Light Bookstore, New York [reading / speaking] 1994 May 19 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Different Light Readers and Writers Conference [reading / speaking] 1993 Dec. 26 -1994 Nov. 11 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Diversionary Theatre, San Diego [production] 1995 Mar. 24 -Apr. 29 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Duke University Mi Gente Asociación de Estudiantes Latinos [speaking / reading] 1995 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Dyke March, San Francisco [social rally] 1994 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Empowering Women of Color Conference, 2d annual, Berkeley [conference panel discussion] 1986 Mar. 1 -2 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Eureka Theatre Company Playwrights' Lab 1990 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Firebrand Books [Bereano, Nancy K.] [publication request] 1991 Aug. 26 -Nov. 12 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Flamboyant Ladies Theatre Company [panel discussion] 1992 May (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Gamboa, Harry [Chusma House Publications] [request for a poem] n.d. (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Getty Center for History of Art and Humanities n.d. (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Gleason, Nick [Coro, a foundation for leadership] [request for interview] 1993 Nov. (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Gomez, Jewelle [reading / speaking] n.d. (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Grinnell College [speaking] 1994 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Guadalupe Cultural Arts Center [reading] 1984 July 10; 1985; 1992 Nov. 10 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Hamilton College, Clinton, NY [reading] 1994 Apr. 26 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Hampshire College [workshop request] 1992 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Hartford Stage Company [production] 1994 -1995 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Harvard University [Martinez, Hilda] [conference request] 1994 -1995 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Hawaii [includes 2 TMs from Kosara-Terry, Gerry. "Autobiography," & "My identity"] 1991 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - High Risk [Scholder, Amy & Ira Silverberg] [request for contribution] 1992 July 24 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Hiram College, Lesbians, Gays, Bisexuals and allies of [Pérez, Mark E. Hricko] [conference] 1995 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Horizons Foundation [philanthropic project request] 1995 Jan. 5 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Humanities Institute, State University of New York, Stony Brook [speaking] 1991 -1992 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - In their voices, San Francisco [reading on behalf of women political prisoners] 1995 Feb. 26 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - International Day in Solidarity with women political prisoners [Beach, Jennifer E.] 1992 Nov. 14 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - International Festival of Puppet Theatre [Dillon, Joanne] [reading / speaking] 1994 July 22 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - International Gay and Lesbian Human Rights Commission [article] 1994 Apr. -May (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - International Lesbian and Gay Associations Conference [reading / speaking] [1 of 3] 1991 June 14 -22 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - International Lesbian and Gay Associations Conference [reading / speaking] [2 of 3] 1991 June 14 -22 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - International Lesbian and Gay Associations Conference [reading / speaking] [3 of 3] 1991 June 14 -22 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Jetter, Alexis. [re: Radical Motherhood] [request for essay revisions] 1994 Oct. 20 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Judith's room [reading / speaking] 1994 Sept. 13 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Kitchen Table Press [reading / speaking] 1994 Oct. 8 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - La Raza Galeria Posada, Sacramento [reading] n.d. (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Latino Chicago Theater Company [production] 1990 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Lesbianas Latinas de Tucson [speaking] 1994 Sept. 16 -17 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Lesbians, Gays, Bisexual People in Medicine [speaking] 1995 Mar. 11 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Lewis & Clark College, Portland, Oregon [production] 1994 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Libros Revolición [reading] 1994 Mar. (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Lopez, Tiffany [interview request] n.d. (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Los Angeles Theatre Center [production] 1989 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Lowell High School [Marin, Kaylah] [interview] n.d. (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - McNaron, Toni & Bonnie Zimmerman, eds. Lesbian Studies. 2d edition [publishing] 1994 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - The Mexican Museum, San Francisco "The Chicano Codices: Encountering Art of the Americas" [publishing] 1992 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Milk Institute, Stanford University [lysack, Andrew] [speaking] 1995 Jan. (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Milligan, Bryce [Daughters of the Fifth Sun] [publishing] 1995 Feb. 11 -Mar. 11 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - M.I.T. Artists-in-Residence Program [Costello, Maureen] 1995 Mar. 6 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Modesto Junior College [reading] 1994 Jan. 21 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Morales, Sylvia [interview] 1994 Feb. (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Movimiento Artistico del Rio Salado (MARS) "Chicanolandia" [publishing] 1992 Sept. (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - NACS Chicana Caucus [Gonzáles, Francisca E.] [reading / speaking] 1994 May 1 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - National Gay and Lesbian Task Force "Fight the Right" [speaking] 1994 Apr. 16 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Nestle, Joan & John Preston, eds. Sister and Brother [publishing] 1993 -1994 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - New College [reading] 1994 Dec. (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - New York State Writers Institute 1992 Oct. 1 -2 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - North Light Books, Santa Rosa, CA [reading / speaking] n.d. (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Orleck, Annelise & Diane Taylor, eds. Radical Motherhood: Mothers, Politics, and Social Change. [publishing] 1993 -1994 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Out Write '92 [conference] 1992 Mar. 20 -22 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Out Write '95 [conference] 1995 Mar. 3 -5 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Outlaw Women [speakout] n.d. (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Pasadena [CA] Public Library [reading] 1994 Oct. 12 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Penguin Book of Gay and Lesbian Plays [Lane, Eric] [publishing] 1994 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Portland State University Lesbian Gay Bisexual Alliance [speaking] n.d. (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Predilections '92: A Gay and Lesbian Literary Conference, University of Alberta 1991 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Public Bodies, Private Space: 2d annual conference on Feminism and Art, San Francisco [speaking] 1994 Feb. 4 -5 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Redwood Cultural Work, Oakland [speaking] 1992 Feb. -Mar. (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Reid, Catherine A. & Kathryn B. Lord, eds. Anthology of Lesbian Relationships [publishing] 1994 Oct. (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Rothenberg, David [interview] n.d. (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - San Francisco Art Institute Summer Art Writing Conference 1994 Aug 8 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - San Francisco Museum of Modern Art [SFMOMA] "Chicano Art: Resistance and Affirmation" [reading / speaking] 1991 Aug. 2 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - San Francisco State University Poetry Center [reading and interview] 1987 Dec. -1991 Oct. (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - San Francisco State University "Writing into the 21st Century" [speaking] 1992 Mar. (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - San Jose State University [DramaDIVAS] n.d. (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Santa Clara University [Novack, Peter] [reading] n.d. (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Santa Monica College [reading] 1994 Apr. (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Seizing the Moment: 4th National Graduate Student Conference on Lesbian, Transgender, Bisexual, & Gay Studies, University of Texas [speaking] 1994 Mar. (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - SF Focus [magazine interview] n.d. (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Smith College [speaking] 1987 Mar. 31 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Speak out! [California State University, Sacramento and Drake University, Iowa] [speaking] 1995 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Stanford University [reading request] 1994 Apr. 21 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Stanford University Lesbian and Gay Grad Students [reading request] 1995 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Stanford University MEChA [Lara, Irene] [speaking] 1994 May (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - State University of New York, Buffalo "Towards an Anti-racist feminism" [speaking request] 1994 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Sternbach, Nancu Saporta, ed. Stages of Life: Latinas in Teatro [publishing request] 1993 -1995 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Task force on cultural diversity, Iowa [speaking] 1992 Feb. (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Tenderloin Women Writers Anthology Goddesses we ain't [Bledsoe, Lucy Jane] [blurb request] 1992 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Testing the limits [interview request] 1993 Dec. (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Texas Lesbian Conference [Salas, Lesley] [speaking request] 1994 Apr. 29 -May 1 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Thompson, Becky & Sangeeta Tyagi. The truth must dazzle gradually [publishing request] 1994 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Trujillo, Carla [Third World Press, Chicana Feminist Theory] [request for contribution] 1994 Sept. 26 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - University of Arizona "Writers in the University and the community" [speaking] 1992 July 15 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - University of California, Berkeley Department of Ethnic Studies [speaking request] n.d. (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - University of California, Berkeley Gay, Lesbian, Bisexual Health [speaking request] 1994 Apr. 9 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - University of California, Davis "Women celebrate their infinite divisions" [speaking / reading] 1995 Jan. (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - University of California, Los Angeles [speaking / interview / reading] 1994 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - University of California, San Francisco Women's Resource Center [speaking request] 1992 May 7 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - University of California, Santa Cruz Seminar on Lesbian Theory [de Lauretis, Teresa] [speaking] 1987 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - University of Cincinnati "A Stage of their own" symposium [speaking request] 1994 Oct. 5 -8 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - University of Colorado, Boulder [speaking request] 1993 -1994 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - University of Colorado, Denver [speaking request] 1993 -1994 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - University of Southern California "Queer Frontiers" [speaking] 1995 Mar. 24 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - University of Texas, Austin "Chicana/o Literary Vibrations" [speaking request] 1990 Nov. 8 -10 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - University of Virginia "Women across cultures, women across boundaries" [speaking request] 1994 Oct. -Nov. (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Ursinus College, Collegeville, PA [speaking request] 1992 Feb. (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - VIVA Lesbian and Gay Latino Artists, Los Angeles [reading] 1994 Mar. 25 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Walker, Rebecca, ed. Third Wave Feminism [publishing request] 1994 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Washington State University "Intersection of Gender, Race, Ethnicity, Class, and Sexual Orientation in Scholarship and Teaching (GRECSO) Conference [speaking] 1995 Feb. 25 -26 (Box 3, Folder 37)